Bhanu Prakash Adhikari

+91 - 8076880659 · bhanuworkfolio@gmail.com · Current location - Gurugram (Haryana), India

LOOKING FOR AN OPPORTUNITY TO START MY CAREER IN HUMAN RESOURCE

I am commited to my work.

A professional designer with 5 years of experience in managing projects & engaging with people. I have completed a Diploma Course in Human Resource Management in order to pursue my career HR industry. Both written & spoken languages which I know are Hindi & English.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Team Building
Decision Making
Problem Solving

Quick Learner of softwares & tasks MS Office - Word, Ppt, Excel

Creativity skills

Clear communication
Proactive and self-motivated
Finding opportunities for productivity

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

1 - Freelancer (Self-employed)

March 2021 - June 2023

As a Freelancing Design Consultant, in Delhi & Hyderabad I provided services in product design, graphic design & Special effects. I was involved in team building & development, utilizing research data & turning them into solutions. I was also involved in media & entertainment projects.

2 - IIT Delhi (IRD design consultant)

November 2020 - February 2021

As an IRD Design Consulted my responsibilities were to help the MSME utilize their consumer research & turm them into business opportunities for them. Other responsibilities were material management, designing company branding, Ui/ Ux design etc.

3 - Khosla Machines Pvt Ltd (Product designer & graphic artist)

January 2019 - January 2020

During my tenure in the company I was responsible for product design, graphic design & training marketing as well as assembly employees about design essentials for our machines. I also worked for operation department for factory space management & other important projects.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

1 - Diploma Course, HR Management Udemy, Inc. 2023 - 2023

- 2 Masters in Anthropology (only result awaited)Indira Gandhi National Open University 2018 2022
- **3 Bachelor of Design (Product Design)** Sushant University 2014 - 2018



"SCAN" the QR code to visit my webiste containing my updated professional works.